Okay, let me start.
Uh, this is my submission for AA slash ML
intern position in PGAGI.
Okay, uh, I have created a talent support hiring assistant which will be helping
us to have a conversation with candidates and get their answers from
us. Then, using text
tag which they have asked for and the position,
you will get details from through this conversations.
I have built this bot here to ask to students.
Let me go through my,
I will be the candidate and the talent support hiring assistant will
be assessing me for this role. So, you will get
those details from me. Okay,
let me start here. Okay,
let's get started. I'm searching for my full name.
Okay, very nice to meet you.
Okay, what's your email address?
and
here I have a give some call back
it will say it is not valid because it is not it is kind
of comparing the pattern like the user name at and the domain name it
has to be in that format
I can't just give number like this, it's also looking a pattern in it,
so I have to give a proper number like this.
If it's cooling, then it's asking for a microphone.
I'm giving 4 over here and the position I'm looking for,
8 over Anna,
West,
then complications,
Chennai, and Popup,
yeah. I'm giving, it's still asking me,
next time. Okay, the slowness,
getting the system a little bit slow,
so we have to bear with it a little So,
there are five questions, which has been answered.
Framed by their experience,
and the text stack they choose, and the, and the question they have enquired
for.
So, we've been basic, two intermediate questions, in which it's a mixture. So,
I have to answer it one by one,
like this. Thank you for
your time,
your profile
has been recorded,
our team is going do this a bit,
and get back to you soon. Have a great day.
Yeah. This is how it's, my,
part of this. Let me show you my,
my source code for this. As I said, ah, my, because it's a loom
recording,
the system is getting a bit
slow, so we have to bear with
it. Yeah.
This And
this
website is, being streamed through Streamlight,
which is a free source here. And also,
I have used a lot of, ah, free sources around,
like, ah, EAPS as well, for, ah, gain phase.
Yeah. For this project itself, that's all for me. Yeah. Thank you.